(Leonard:)But we were thinking more of us
maybe living together with...
(Leonard:)...not you.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand.
(Sheldon:)How could we all live together
if I'm not there?
Look, I know this is...
this is change,
(Leonard:)-and that sounds scary--
-Where are you going to go?
(Sheldon:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)We just started to think about this.
(Leonard:)Maybe I'll move in with Penny,
(Leonard:)or maybe she and I'll take this
place, you can move across the hall.
(Sheldon:)Move across the hall?
(Sheldon:)Did you take a marijuana?
(Penny(on phone):)No, I did not.
(Sheldon:)Did you get hit on the head
with a coconut?
(Howard:)-No.
-Well, then, I'm all out of guesses.
(Sheldon:)What? Me move across the hall-- Why
would you even suggest such a thing?
(Leonard:)Because I love Penny, and want
to give her the life she deserves.
(Sheldon:)I see.
(Sheldon:)You're putting your future
bride's happiness above mine.